Let's make dreams! We can do it!
Let's make dreams! Change my world!
kizuite shimattara mou tomaranai
There's no turning back once we start
atarashii sekai kitto ne tsukamaeru yo
Looking for a new world, and I know we'll find one
wakuwaku shichattara kitto we can't stop da ne
Once we start having fun I just know we can't stop
issho dattara watashi mo odoru ne
As long as we're together I can dance too
yume no door
The door of dreams
sanmi ittai de nara hiraku to shinjiteru
It will open for the three of us, I believe it will
dakara here we go
So here we go
naisho no passion
Our secret passion
jouseki datte kiseki ni kawaru hazu yo
Will turn our "run-of-the-mill" into miracles
tsuitekite yo ne
Come on along
tsuiteku ne
Come on
mahou mitai na PARTY TIME
To our magical PARTY TIME
dare datte minna motteru no
You and me, we all have one
hontou no jibun kagayaku place
A place where we can really shine
kaetai no nara
Want to change things?
negawanakya
Make a wish
sagashite
Look for it
kokoro no oku no omoi
A feeling from deep within
kanaete
Make it true
kakushiteta hontou no smile
The true smile you hid
osaerarenai yo
Can't be held back anymore
kitto minna
No one can
dakara jounetsu no mama
Give in to the passion and
Sing! Sing!
utatte miyou
Let's sing together
kawatte iku kara my way
I'm changing! My way!
akenakute namaru yori
Don't give up so fast
watashi motte issho ni waraou
Come on and laugh with us
shiranakatta sekai ga
A world we never knew
yume no door
The door of dreams
hiraita mukou ni
Revealed it to us
dare datte minna motteru no
You and me, we all have one
hontou no jibun kagayaku place
A place where we can really shine
mitsuketa no nara oshiete ne
If you found yours, do tell
negatta
If you wished
kokoro no oku no omoi
A feeling from deep within
kanaeyou
Make it true
kakusenai saikou no smile
The best smile is one you can't hide
afuredashichau yo
Can't contain
kitto minna
No one can
hora ne jounetsu no mama
So give in to the passion and
Sing! Sing!
utatte miyou
Let's sing together
kawatte ikun da my world
We're changing my world!
onna no ko mo
All you girls
otoko no ko mo
And boys too
utaou yo
Let's sing!
Let's change the world!